# **UBIA OKECUKWU JOSEPH**

# **SUMMARY**

I have 5 years of experience of Hospitality Management at various reputable organizations. I am looking for the opportunity to advance to a Management position where I can use my skills in developing strategies and leading a team. Highly organized in communication, interpersonal, problem solving and working with team members. I have a proven ability to participate and handle needs of clients, I can also successfully manage multiple tasks prioritize effectively to achieve goals.

## **EXPERIENCE**

BLACKSAMLTD—MARYLAND, Lagos. FEBRUARY 2019- PRESENT

Team Leader, Staff Trainer, Production Manager, Cashier, Customer Services

- Monitored work-flows to ensure accuracy in data entry processes and provide timely resolutions when issues arise.
- Notified supervisors of overarching customer and team member concerns.
- Mentored and coached team members to ensure successful performance.
- Mentored junior staff by providing advice on how to handle challenging situations effectively.

DIGITAL SMART – V.I., Lagos Nigeria. MAY 2019 - JANUARY 2019.

INTERN – AS DIGITAL EDUCATOR

- Created computer-generated artwork using design software.
- Determined size and arrangement of illustrative materials and copy.
- Collaborated with marketing team to develop concepts for campaigns and promotions.
- Developed a range of web page designs incorporating animation, video and other multimedia elements.
- Optimized graphics for web usage through image optimization techniques.
- Assisted senior designers in production processes by providing technical support when needed.

## **EDUCATION**

UNIVERSITY OF LAGOS, AKOKA, LAGOS National Diploma. 2016 – 2018

SOCIAL ADMINISTRATION AND DEVELOPMENT - S.D.A

PROJECT W.R.A.P. COVENANT CENTER. VI, LAGOS. *Diploma Certificate.* 2016 – 2018

WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT

DIGITAL SMART, V.I, LAGOS Diploma Certificate. JAN.2020 – JAN.2021

DIGITAL EDUCATOR

## **CONTACT**

Phone: (+234) 8075100681 <u>ubiajoseph@gmail.com</u> <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Portfolio</u> Lagos, Nigeria.

## **SKILLS**

#### **TOOLS**

Visual Studio Code (HTML AND CSS), Adobe XD, Canva Slack, Word and Docs

#### INTERPERSONAL

Empathy

Creativity

Growth Mindset

Critical thinking

Adaptive Learning

Problem Solving

Team Spirit

**Communication Skills** 

## **LANGUAGES**

English - First Language Igbo-Native

#### **INTERESTS**

Music, Drawing, Art, Travel

### REFERENCE

DR. J.O AWOYINFA University of Lagos, Akoka, Lagos state.

Phone: (+234) 8023222096

MRS. OKECHUKWU .C. Command Secondary School, Ikeja, Lagos.

Phone: (+234) 8026545827